Speaker 1 (lower-pitched voice): - Carrie Lake joins us. She's running for the United States Senate in Arizona. That's where she was just a little while ago, Kamala Harris. Your reaction and good to see you tonight.
Speaker 2: - Ooh, my blood's boiling right now. When you gave those numbers, I heard those numbers earlier. You know, it's 425,000 convicted
Speaker 3: criminals
Speaker 3: 14,000
Speaker 4: murderers, 16,000 rapists. And those are the government numbers, so you know they're even higher than that. I'm surprised she didn't call Joe
Speaker 3: Biden and say, "We did it, Joe, we did it, we destroyed this country," because that's exactly what she has done. As she stands here by the border, there are people all over this country probably ready to throw something at their TV.
Speaker 5: Everybody who's lost a loved one,
Speaker 5: From fentanyl poisoning, everybody who's lost a loved one to crime that a migrant, an illegal immigrant, you know, committed on them. Every city that's turned into a sanctuary city, every state that's turned into a sanctuary state. That woman right there on your screen, walking along the border,
Speaker 4: trying to do a photo op, is responsible for. She's the border czar. We can't forget that, even though she's trying to bury that.
Speaker 4: and for her to come down to the border right before the election and try to act like she gives a damn and pardon my anger on this greg but we are feeling the effects of this terrible border policy that she caused right there here in arizona and i've talked to so many moms and dads who've lost a 16 year old son or a 19 year old daughter and for her to stand there and act like she cares about our border it's shameful
Speaker 4: And you're right, it's an impeachable offense. It's treasonous what they've done here on our border. We don't have a border anymore. It's just a cartel zone.
-
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): You know, if we could re-rack that video, I saw something kind of interesting when she was walking along. She was totally despondent looking at the ground. Take it full if you don't mind. No, no, no, no. At the beginning portion of this thing, yeah, she's just kind of head down like a bored kid on a tour
of
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): a museum that she doesn't want to be attending. She's not even looking at the guy. I know later she's going to make eye contact, but that kind of reflects her general attitude. I don't think she likes being there. Her base doesn't want her there. The base wants it wide open. Joe
Speaker 7: Biden's promised to, urged people to surge the border. Remember that one?
Speaker 8: Right. Well, she doesn't want to look up and look at the border wall because she wants that
Speaker 4: border wall gone. You know, remember, Joe Biden and Kamala Harris, we had three hundred and twenty five million dollars worth of materials to finish or at least partially finish that border wall. And they gave
it away
Speaker 4: for pennies on the dollar. So she's probably standing next to the border wall in her head, wondering how quickly she
can
Speaker 3: get rid of the wall that is there so that there's more space
Speaker 5: for people to pour in illegally. It's really despicable what they have done.
Speaker 5: I'm surprised she could even find
Speaker 4: the border today because she hasn't been able to find it for, you know, three and a half years. And to come to Arizona, she's been to Arizona, by the way, probably a dozen times, and she's never bothered to go to the border, even though this is the state with more fentanyl pouring in than any other state. This is the state where we've watched as thousands of military aged Chinese men have poured across in the open gaps, where we've watched
Speaker 5: children being trafficked.
Speaker 5: And that woman right there, Kamala Harris, has lost track of 320,000 little ones, babies, children who've been trafficked across the border who are missing now. And that is really, truly blood
Speaker 9: on her hands. So,
Carrie
Speaker 10: Lake, we have, what,
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): a little over a month before your Senate election, of course, the presidential election as well. You know, you're in a very competitive race, but I sense you've
Speaker 11: got momentum. tell us a little bit, give us the lay of the land and anything we should know about your
opponent
Speaker 11: or anything else?
Speaker 12: - Well, let me tell you what you just saw with Kamala Harris, my opponent is a male version of
Speaker 4: that. He's a male version, he's voted with her dead-end, disastrous policies 100% of the time. I think he's the only person in all of Congress that's voted 100% of the time with Joe Biden and Kamala Harris. He's pro-open borders, and he wants to give
Speaker 5: everybody who's come across this border
Speaker 5: amnesty immediately uh asylum and he wants them to vote he's actually voted for that already he wants federal dollars going to these sanctuary cities and he said he could never imagine a case that he'd want to deport anyone i'll tell you
Speaker 4: what we need to do all of these people who poured in during this biden invasion
Speaker 4: need to go back to their homeland. We've got to save our homeland. The only way to do that is to send these people who've invaded our country back to their homeland. And he's actually, you know, I want to confront the cartels. He is controlled by the cartels. His own father was a Colombian
Speaker 5: drug trafficker. And so he's got links to the cartel. And that is very concerning, and it should be
Speaker 4: concerning for everybody out there. This is an important race. My internal polling has showed us
Speaker 4: up over Ruben Gallego since June. You know, these public polls are really meant to try to take the oxygen out of our movement on the ground here in Arizona. The people of Arizona don't like that guy that you see on your screen. Well, they don't like either of those guys. And they don't want to have a wide open border anymore. They don't want to have the cartels controlling our state. So I feel comfortable going into this election. We're debating. I will be debating Ruben Gallego on October 9th. And that's when ballots are going to be in
Speaker 4: mailboxes, and we hope that people will get those ballots turned in. And we're going to show up big and strong here in Arizona. We are registering thousands of people, more in the Republican Party than in the Democrat Party, and the young people are coming over as well, realizing that Ruben Gallego would be a disaster for their future because he is a Marxist who wants open borders and communism here in America. Carrie Lake, on
Speaker 6 (lower-pitched voice): fire as usual. We appreciate it so much. Go to CarrieLake.com and good luck. Let's stay in touch. We'll see you soon, okay? Thank you. You bet.